Three weeks of planning is crazy! They actually want to give each of our players two bundles of their choice.
For our part, we can grab some fries from Hunting Hour, and Tesla Circle selects two bundles.
Then the activity P V is like this, and then the gun skin during hunting should be red,
Brothers, you can take a look. Then grab some French fries, which should be, uh, divided into your hands. Besides that,
Many brothers were shocked when they saw the news. Is this still the Delta operation I am familiar with?
And, there is more than one skin in the bundle. In addition, keep
Zangyue, when you start the treasure event, you will definitely get red materials, the kind that Kua Kua Mo Big Red will produce.
There are three maps for Treasure Moon, and each corresponding map has been sorted out for the brothers.
Then there are twelve points in the dam, and then there are twelve treasure points in the eight divisions.
There are still twelve treasure hiding spots in Changdongxigu. Then this is the treasure chest, let me show it to the brothers.
If you happen to get treasure map No. 8, hey, then you can open the box and interact accordingly.
Red quality materials must be issued. By then, hey, the whole map people should get the signal,
So back and forth, brothers can look forward to a wave of treasure-hunting operations. In addition,
Artifact containers can also drop treasure maps, and searching for the specified container will also drop corresponding treasures.
Then the treasure hunting team will also explode.
Finally, brothers, do you think, hey, if Delta sends these two sets of Kunpeng King and Bianhong,
Will the pressure go to the next door?